Resha Puspita Dewi

Bandung, Indonesia | +62821 3032 0607 | reshapuspitadewi@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Undergraduate Student in Information System and Technology major with internship experience as Web Developer. Enjoyed content creation as an instrument to support a learning process. Confident to gain new experiences in a sector that can empower people to improve their level of needs continuously.

EXPERIENCE

Loker Programmer (Medan, Indonesia)

Front End Programmer Intern (August 2020 - October 2020)

- Develop interactive website using ReactJS in collaborated with cross-functional teams
- Integrate Front-End components with RESTful API to develop fully functioning web page

ProBotDev Sdn Bhd (Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia)

Scrum Master Apprenticeship (April 2019 - June 2019)

- Responsible to provide project boards for software engineer (SE) teams
- Enable scrum implementation in a team with 4 members
- Collaborate with product owner to deliver instruction to the team

EDUCATION

Institut Teknologi Bandung (2017-Present)

Bachelor of Engineering

SKILLS

- Basic programming
- Web development: Ruby, Javascript
- Mobile (Android) development: Java, Kotlin
- Prototyping tools: Adobe XD, Figma

TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS

- Electives Lite x Tokopedia Academy (June 2021)
 - Testing in Scale with Tokopedia Engineering Productivity Course
- Generasi GIGIH by Yayasan Anak Bangsa Bisa (YABB) (May 2021-August 2021)
 Backend Engineer
- Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka (February 2021-July 2021)
 Mobile (Android) Development Participant
- Telkom Digital Talent Incubator (DTI) (September 2020-December 2020)
 Backend Developer Talent
- Impact Byte (June 2020-August 2020)

Full Stack Web Graduate

VOLUNTEER AND ORGANIZATIONS

HMIF ITB (March 2019-March 2021)

Academic and Welfare Staff

- Responsible to input study resources into shared drive throughout the semester
- Responsible to share information related to academics and scholarship with the members.

Lingkar Sastra ITB (November 2017-May 2020)

Head of Infrastructure & Household Division (2019-2020) Member of Craftmanship Division (2018-2019)

- Have a discussion with the member to appreciate literary works
- Responsible to organize seminars and competitions related to literature.
- Responsible to accommodate the literary works of members to be published into physical work.

SOCIAL MEDIA

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/reshapuspita/

Github: github.com/renvelvet

Medium: medium.com/@renmaar